Guide to the George Borchardt Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II
  - English Language Publishers and Agents
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Wilson, Andrew (Box 84)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Wilson, Derek "Hugh Preston" (Box 84)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Woodman, Dorothy (Box 84)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: World Coin Catalogue. (Box 84)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Wright, David & Patrick Swift (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: 1970-1980 (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Betjeman, Sir John (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Evans, Jocelyn (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Feversham, Charles Antony Peter Duncombe, 6th Baron (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Gaillardet, Frederic (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Godson, John (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Lindsay, Cressida (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Mutwa, Credo Vusa'mazulu (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: O'Callaghan, Sean (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Osborne, Charles (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Rae, Hugh C. (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Strachey, Lytton (Box 84)
    - Anthony Blond Ltd: Tolstoy, Leo (Box 84)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Baity, Elizabeth Chesley (Box 85)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Banks, Lynne Reid (Box 85)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Bolt, David L. (Box 85)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Bond, Brian (Box 85)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Cannon, John (Box 85)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Carey, Elizabeth (Sue R. Bridge) "Rosemary Newman" (Box 85)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Churchward, John (Box 85)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Dally, Peter (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Derry, John (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Dewhurst, Eileen (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Dillon, Eilis (Mrs Vivian H.S. Mercier) (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Dumas, Alexandre (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Enright, Dennis Joseph (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Flower, Pat (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Footman, David (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Forman, Joan (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Forrester, Larry (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Foster, David (Box 86)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Foxall, Raymond Jehdiada Campbell (Box 87)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Frewer, Glyn (Box 87)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Garrett, Richard (Box 87)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Gilbert, Anna (Box 87)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Glaskin, Gerry M. (Box 87)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Graber, Gerry S. (Box 87)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Graham, Harriet (Box 87)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Harrison, Elizabeth (Box 87)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Harrison, Fred (Box 87)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Hebblethwaite, Peter (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Heley, Veronica "Victoria Thorne" & "Tamar Burkin" (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Hemingway, Amanda (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Hill, Douglas & Gail Robinson (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Hollins, Arthur (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Holroyd, Stuart (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Hutchison, Harold Frederick (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Jacobs, Arthur (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Jon, Montague (John Montague Dovener) (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Kettle, Pamels "Jocelyn Kettle" (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Koch, Christopher J. (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Lefebure, Molly (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Lemarchand, Elizabeth (Box 88)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Leslie, Josephine "R.A. Dick" (Box 89)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Longmate, Norman (Box 89)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Macksey, Kenneth (Box 89)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Mann, Jessica (Jessica Thomas) (Box 89)
    - Bolt & Watson Ltd Authors' Agents: Mayhew, Elizabeth (Joan Bear) (Box 89)
    - Calder & Boyars Ltd. (Box 89)
    - John Calder (Publishers) Ltd. (Box 89)
    - Andre Deutsch Ltd.: Grzimek, Bernhard (Box 89)
    - Andre Deutsch Ltd.: Mott, Michael (Box 89)
    - Andre Deutsch Ltd.: Wyndham, Violet L. H. (Box 89)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers, 1965-1978 (Box 89)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Blake, William (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Boucher, Alan (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Butler, William (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Clark, Leonard (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Duddington, Natalie (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Garvey, Ric (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Gunnell, Bryn (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Kay, Mara (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Mander, Raymond & Joe Mitchenson (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers North, Joan (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Pope, Ray (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Quayle, Eric (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Robinson, Michael (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Tynan, Kenneth (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Walker, Victoria (Box 90)
    - Rupert Hart-Davis Limited Publishers Westwood, Jennifer (Box 90)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Aitchison, Jean (Box 90)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Alexnader, Conel Hugh O'Donel (Box 90)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Allen, John E. & Joan Bruce (Box 90)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Alliss, Peter (Box 90)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Paul Trevillion (Box 90)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Allsop, Kenneth (Box 90)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Alvin, Juliette (Box 90)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Ambler, C. Gifford (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Anderson, Ann (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Anderson, Arthur James (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Anderson, Bob (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Andrew, Prudence (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Arnold, H.J.P. (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Ash, William (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Asquith, Lady Cynthia Mary Evelyn (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Badcock, C.R. (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Balfour, James (William B. Hepburn) (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Barnaby, Kenneth C. (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Barrington, Jonah (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Bass, Howard (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Bauman, Zygmunt (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Beare, George (Box 91)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Bennett, Ralph (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Bentley, Joyce (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Berggren, Sigvard (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Betteridge, Anne (Margaret Potter) (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Bharati, Agehananda (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Biology series (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Bishop, Sheila (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Biss, Andreas (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Bond, Brian (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Bourne, Hester (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Bradshaw, S. (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Brander, Michael (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Brier, Alan & Ian Robinson (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Brodrick, Alan Houghton (Box 92)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Buytendijk, Frederick (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Butler, Bill (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Butler, Richard (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Caldwell, A. & Jeffrey N. Wood (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Caldwell, John (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Cheiro (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Chesser, Eustace (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Christie's Review. (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Ciliates & Pycnogonids. (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Cohen, J.M. & J.F. Phipps (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Coleman, John (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Coleman, Terry (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Conn, Stewart (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Copeland, James (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Coutts-Smith, Kenneth (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Craig, Bill (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Crossley, Anthony (Box 93)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Curling, Audrey (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Curtis, Susannah (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: David, Janina (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: David-Neel, Alexandra (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Davies, John B. (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Del Vasto, Lanza (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Denbigh, Kenneth George (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Dictionary of Difficult Words. (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Dillon, Francis (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Diringer, David (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Dobereiner, Peter (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Doxiadis, Constantine (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Dubcek, Alexander (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Dunne, Lee (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Durisch, Peter (Box 94)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Eastcott, Michal J. (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Eastvale, Margaret (Mrs B.M. Carr) (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Edwards, Robert & Patrick Steptoe (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Ellis, Audrey (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Encyclopedia. (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Featherstone, Donald F. (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Fellowes, Catherine (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Feuerstein, Georg A. (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Fletcher, Geoffrey (Box 95)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Forsyth, Frederick (Box 96)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Franklin, Olga (Box 96)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Fraser, Frances (Box 96)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Friendly, Alfred (Box 96)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Froissard, Jean & Lily Powell (Box 96)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Frost, Kelman (Box 96)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Fry, Pete (Box 96)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Garrett, Richard (Box 97)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Gasking, Elizabeth (Box 97)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Geach, Peter T. (Box 97)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: General correspondence, 1967-1974 (Box 97)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: General correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 98)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Gerassimov, N.M. (Box 98)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Germany, Jo (Box 98)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Gibbon, Lewis Grassic (Box 98)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Giles, F.J. (Box 98)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Goodman, Jonathan (Box 98)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Gordon, John (Box 98)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Govinda, Anagarika (Li Gotami Govinda) (Box 98)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Gray, Robert (Box 99)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Griffiths, Helen (Box 99)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Guenther, Traus H. (Box 99)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Guthrie, John (Box 99)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Hadfield, John (Box 99)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Hamilton, Alex (Box 99)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Hamsik, Dusan (Box 99)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Harrington, A.P. (Box 99)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Hyers, M. Conrad (Box 99)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Inber, Vera -Inquiries, 1980 (Box 100)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Jacobs, John (Box 100)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: James, Edwin (Box 100)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: James, Dame Naomi Christine Power (Box 100)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Jeffries, Roderic, "Peter Alding", "Jeffrey Ashford", "Roderic Greame" (Box 100)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Jobson, William Hamilton (Box 101)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Jones, Bradshaw (Box 101)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Joseph, Helen (Box 101)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Keller, W. Phillip (Box 101)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Kelly, J.F. (Box 101)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Kenton, Warren Derek "Z'ev ben Shimon Halevi" (Box 101)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Knight, Alanna H. (Box 101)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Knox, Bill, "Michael Kirk", "Robert McLeod", "Noah Webster" (Box 101)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Knox, Bill (Box 102)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Koestler, Arthur (Box 102)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Lang, Ian (Box 102)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Lannoy, Richard & Harry Baines (Box 102)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Latham, John Wilkinsin & R.J. Wilkinson Latham (Box 102)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Lee, Arthur Gould (Box 102)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Leishman, James Blair (Box 102)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Leslie, Anita (Box 103)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Lewis, Hilda (Box 103)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Lillie, Helen (Helen Lillie Marwick) (Box 103)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Linder, Mariella (Box 103)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Longford, Francis Aungier Pakenham, 7th Earl of (Box 103)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: O'Neill, T.P. (Box 103)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Lubis, Mochtar (Box 103)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Ludlam, Harry (Box 103)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Luk, Charles (Box 103)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: McBride, William (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: McCartney, James (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: McClean, Tom (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: McCormick, Donald (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: McCulloch, Alex (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: MacCulloch, John (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: McCutcheon, Hugh (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: MacDiarmid, Hugh (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: McIntosh, Christopher (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Macmillan, Norman (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: MacSweeney, Barry (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Madden, Anne Wakefield (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Maddocks, Margaret (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Mair, George B. (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Makin, Irene (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Mannin, Ethel (Box 104)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Marsden, Peter (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Marshall, Peter (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Martin, Kingsley (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Mason, Haydn T. (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Mead, W.R. & E.H. Brown (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Meadows, Rose (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Mellows, Joan (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Men in Action series. (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Merilees, William (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Meyler, Desiree (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Milani, Milena (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Molesworth, Roger (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Moore, Bobby (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Moray, Neville (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Morris, Desmond & Ramona (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Morrison, James (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Morry, W. Ritson & W. Melville Mitchell (Box 105)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Moseley, Maboth (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Mottram, Tony (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Mountfort, Guy (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Mountjoy, Alan B. & B.C. Embleton (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Muller, Robert (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Munro Smith, R. (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Murphy, Genevieve (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Muskett, Netta (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Naismith, Marion (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Naydler, Merton (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Neill, Robert (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Neterclift, Beryl (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Norcliffe, G.B. (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Nurmi, Martin (Box 106)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Offerings, A-Z, 1980 (Box 107)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Oldroyd, Harold (Box 107)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Osmond, Andrew (Box 107)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Owen, Rosamund (Box 107)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Pask, Gordon (Box 107)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Pedder, I.J. & G. Wynne (Box 107)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Philipp, Elliot Elias (Box 107)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Pinto, Vivian de Sola (Box 107)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Pope John Paul II (Karol Wojtyla) (Box 108)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Popular dogs series. (Box 108)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Pred, Allan R. (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Prem, Sri Krishna (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Preston, Adrian (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Pribam, Karl & Mervin Gill (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Pringle, Mia Kelimer (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Proust letters. (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Proysen, Alf (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Pullan, J.M. (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Racster, Olga (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Ramsay, Joan & Hartley (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Read, Elfreida (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Reed, Graham (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Reeman, Douglas "Alexander Kent" (Box 109)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Rendell, Ruth (Box 110)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Renier, Elizabeth (Box 110)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Phodes, H.T.F. (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Rivers, Anne (Patricia Louise Dalton) (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Roe, Sir Alliott Verdon (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Rolt-Wheeler, Francis (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Romanov, A.I., pseud. (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Rosenthal, Gerard (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Ross, Angus (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Rossi, Alfred (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Rowe, Christopher (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Roy, Archie (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Ruell, Patrick (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Sambursky, Shuel (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Gangharakshita, Bhikshu (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Santa Maria, Jack (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Saunders, Vivien (Box 111)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Schumann, Wolfgang (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Schwarz, Boris (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Scott, George (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Scott. Tom & Geoffrey Cousins (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Seth, Ronald (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Seymour, Miranda (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Simmie, J.M. (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Slanska, Josefa (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Smith, John E. (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Sontheimer, Kurt & Wilhelm Bleek (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Sparrow, Gerald (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Spiral series. (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Sporne, K.R. (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Steiner, Irene (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Steinhoff, Johannes (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Stevenson, W.C. (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Stoddard, Alan (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Strick, Philip (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Swinton, Philip Cunliffe-Lister, 1st Earl of (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Sykes, John (Box 112)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Tack, Alfred (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Tapsell, R.F. (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Temple, Nigel (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Tester, M.H. (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Tew, Brian (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Thackeray, Alec (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Thorndike, Russell (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Thorpe, Sylvia (June Sylvia Thimblethorpe) (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Townsend, John Rowe (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Trevillion, Paul (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Trollope, Joanna (Box 113)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group Limited: Ullyett, Kenneth (Box 114)